Um, well, in my defense,
I tell everybody.
Why would you say that?!
(Raj:)We were having a conversation
about past lovers.
We weren't lovers! Come on.
(Penny:)Everyone knows
we didn't sleep together.
(Penny:)We got drunk
and fooled around.
(Penny:)Why couldn't you just
leave me out of it?
(Raj:)Well, we were being honest.
(Raj:)You would leave me
out of the conversation
(Raj:)with the next guy
if you dump Leonard?
(Leonard:)Why say it?
Yes!
(Raj:)Well, I would never
leave you off my list,
(Raj:)and not just
(Raj:)because, without you,
(Raj:)we're playing fast and loose
with the word "list."
(Penny:)Well, good job.
Now she hates me.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Penny:)Great.
(Sheldon:)On the bright side,
that Oxford study was right.
(Sheldon:)One friend down.
(Sheldon:)I wonder who you're going
to lose next.
(Raj:)You, okay? It's you.
You're-you're next!
(Sheldon:)No. You're crazy about me.
(Penny:)I don't know what Emily's
so upset about anyway.